getthebigpicture.net 2013-04-12

# Privacy - Movie News | Trailers | Posters

PRIVACY POLICY FOR THE BIG PICTURE  GetTheBigPicture

**PRIVACY POLICY FOR THE BIG PICTURE**

GetTheBigPicture.net

Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

There are instances where a user may provide specific personal information in response to a survey, contest, purchase agreement, or registration questionnaire. For such programs, The Big Picture (or a third party working in conjunction with The Big Picture) acquires this information on behalf of the advertiser client. This information is used by the client so the user can receive the goods or services requested or won. When requested, The Big Picture may employ this information in a compiled format without identifying users specifically to provide to the advertiser client precise profiles of the types of individuals responding.

With respect to ad servers: The Big Picture maintains relationships with other companies that place advertisements on our web pages. By visiting GetTheBigPicture.Net, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

Should this privacy policy change, those alterations will be reflected on this page on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use.

For questions about this policy, please contact Fave Company, Inc. at [ admin@favecompany.com](mailto:admin@favecompany.com).
